Yeah. Hey, what's up, Blake?
>> What's going on, guys?
>> Not a whole lot. So, obviously the the
elephant in the room here is Spencer is
a part of the team still. What is your
understanding of how this is going to
work going forward?
>> Uh, one more time, would you say?
>> So, Spencer obviously coming back from
being hurt. He's rehabbing, but what is
your understanding like? What did the
Colts tell you to expect about, I guess,
both your roles moving forward and how
this is going to work?
Um, I mean, obviously I know Spencer's
in the room. Me and him are are good
buddies. And so, um, you know, from what
I've been told, I'm coming in to, uh, to
go to work and and try to win a job just
like, um, just like it'd be if if I was
anywhere else. So, um, you know, I'm
excited to be back in Indie and and, um,
you know, kind of continue to keep the
ball rolling like I was able to end the
season.
>> Chop, go ahead.
Yeah, Blake, I I guess what you you had
to take the approach last year that all
you can do is what you did and then it's
on the Colts to see if they wanted to
move forward. I assume looking back you
did all you could do to prove yourself.
>> Yeah. U obviously I feel like I put my
best foot forward um those last those
last five weeks of the season and um and
so yeah, you know, like like I like I
said at the end of the season, like kind
of the last time I talked to you guys is
just continue to to to be the best I
can. But I mean, regardless of the
situation and uh that's that's always
kind of the motto, I guess you could
say. So, just going to continue to try
to be my best and and uh you know, push
to uh you know, continue to be be more
consistent and um you know, continue to
better myself and and uh you know, do my
job to help the team.
>> James
>> Blake, did you have other opportunities?
>> Yeah, I mean, you worked through the
free agency process. Uh coming back to
India was always um I guess my number
one um you know choice. So uh really
value the the way organization handles
things and treats people and and uh you
know value the room with Luke and Rigo
and and uh Mace and all the coaches. So
um you know I was I I'm excited you know
for this opportunity and everything that
you know you know I can have the
opportunity to go improve this year. So,
um, you know, like like I said, I'm
excited to go out and work and and, uh,
yeah, there were opportunities. Um, but
I mean, at the end of the day, I I chose
to come back here and and, uh, you know,
I'm excited.
>> One more followup. Um, what do you think
led to the success that you had here
last year with the Colts and and how
quickly were you able to get acclimated
to the environment?
>> Yeah, you know, that's a great question.
um you know I guess when I look at it
from like a technical side I didn't I
didn't change a single thing from what
um I was doing slash always have done.
So, um, that's kind of was what, you
know, made me the most proud is the fact
that, you know, I stuck to myself and
and what I knew works for me and and,
uh, but I think what made it work in
Indie so much and so so well, like so
quickly was the fact that I was able to
get comfortable with everybody and
everything. And, um, you know, when when
you you know, when you when you just
kind of prove yourself again, that
that's another thing I enjoyed is just
the the opportunity to prove myself
again and and show everybody what I can
do. you know, I really I really love
that kind of stuff. And, you know, just
just as much as like the workout back in
the building on on when I had to work
out on that Tuesday versus um you know,
in that next practice on the Thursday,
like I I really enjoy those competitive
situations where I get to uh prove
myself to everybody. You know, I really
uh that's kind of what keeps me going.
>> Jake, go ahead.
>> Yeah. So, when you got here last year,
the Colts had already kind of started to
to falter and they had the losing streak
at the end of the year, but everyone's
kind of banking on the strong first half
of the year they had. So, from your
understanding, you've only kind of seen
the the losing of it, but what do you
see in this team that I guess makes you
confident that they'll get back to
rolling how they were in the first half
of last year?
Yeah, you know, obviously, like I said,
I didn't get to see or be a part of um
the first half of last year, but u I
guess you know, watched it from afar and
uh just from watching it from from when
I was on another team in the league,
just the the energy and enthusiasm that
the guys had and the team played with.
Um I mean, points were getting scored
left and right that the team was flying
around and and uh you know, there's
there's a a a huge feeling of like
belief from what you know, I feel like I
could see. And so, um, you know, coming
into it now and being a part of it, uh,
I I mean, I see a group that bringing a
lot of the same guys back and and a lot
of lot of lot of difference makers that,
you know, I know we have on the team and
that, uh, you know, I'm excited to play
with this year and and continue to get
to know and build those relationships
with.